

WEB DEVELOPER · FRONT END EXPERT

House No:651/3, Road: Kamal khan Road, Ibrahimpur, Mirpur-14, 1216, Dhaka, Bangladesh

🛘 +8801745386138 | 🗷 idlasifmahmud@gmail.com | 🏕 portfolio.themifiy.com/ | 🖸 AsifMahmudPallab | 🛅 asif-mahmud-13a207180

"Be the change that you want to see in the world."

Summary.

I have 5+ years of experience specializing in Frontend development, i worked on many websites and web applications. and I have 10+ HTML templates, and 5+ React Templates approved at ThemeForest. I have experience with React Native. I am Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Specialization ____

Front-end: React, Redux, React Router, React Native, PWA, HTML5, CSS, SASS, Photoshop, Figma

Framework: Reactjs, NextJs, Bootstrap, React material ui, React Native

Programming: JavaScript, Es6

Work Experience

EkkBaz Bangladesh Pvt. Ltd.

SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER (FRONT END LEAD AND REACT JS DEVELOPER)

- Front end team lead position, work's E-commerce, and Admin panel and also Native app
- Play key role, and helping create full eCommerce ecosystem with mobile App

Happihub LTD Banasree, Dhaka

WEB DEVELOPER (REACT JS, MUI DESIGN)

· Front end team lead position, works in house product

• Play key role, and helping the team to Admin panel, landing page, and client's project

Sonali Information Technology LTD

WEB DESIGNER & DEVELOPER (FRONT END LEAD AND REACT JS DEVELOPER)

- Front end team lead position, work's envato marketplace
- Play key role, and helping team to build html, reactis templete, and client's project
- Working Some Mobile application frontend by React Native with Team

Themelooks Mirpur, Dhaka

WEB DESIGNER

• Creating HTML templete from themeforest

• Wordpress friendly design and Mobile responsive design

Elegent Technology Limited

WEB DESIGNER

- · Creating HTML templete from themeforest
- Testing a HTML CSS framework Offra, It's there Own Project

Niketon, Dhaka

Sep. 2018 - April. 2019

Razzak plaza, Mogbazar, Dhaka

May. 2022 - Continue

Nov. 2021 - April 2022

Mohammadpur, Dhaka

April. 2019 - Oct. 2021

Jan. 2018 - Aug. 2018

Education

Lakshmipur govt college Lakshmipur

B.S.C IN PHYSICSMar. 2009 - Aug. 2013

Lakshmipur govt college Lakshmipur

HIGHER SECONDARY SCHOOL CERTIFICATE jun. 2007 - Jun. 2009

Poura shahid smrity academy

Lakshmipur

Secondary school certificate jun. 2007

DECEMBER 31, 2022 ASIF MAHMUD · RÉSUMÉ